Do you want subtitles for any video?
-=[ ai.OpenSubtitles.com ]=-
I'm here to pick up Tu Polla.
Your dick.
Hello. Ruben.
You know who I am?
Then you know this is
the last place I want to be.
Then why are you here?
I heard you were going to
drop your appeal.
SJLP sent you.
I told them I'm done.
I came to tell you one thing...
...that your pain has meaning.
Your pain. you can embrace it
and turn it into strength.
I never killed anyone
until they stuck me in this fucking place.
This place gets to you!
Just last week. I was right where you are.
You think your story is over.
but it isn't.
Maybe it isn't even your story.
Maybe you have a much
greater purpose... underneath.
Ruben!
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org